It's been a while.
久しぶりだ
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Where are you going?
どこに行こうとしてるの?
Come here.
こっち来い
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Sorry.
すいません
Come here.
こっち来い
There are people.
人おるわ
Come here.
こっち来い
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Don't run away anymore.
もう逃げんなって
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Sorry.
すいません
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Sorry.
すいません
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Where are you trying to go?
ど こ に行こうとしてるの?
yes.
はい
what are you doing
何してる
of?
の?
what are you doing?
何 してるの?
yes.
はい
Come here.
こっち来い
Alcohol.
お 酒
How are you doing?
どうしてるの?
yes.
はい
what are you doing?
何 して る の?
I want to quit this hole.
こういう穴辞めたいです
What are you quitting?
何を辞めるの?
I want to quit.
辞めたいです
What are you quitting?
何を辞めるの?
I also borrowed it from my mother.
母さんにも借りかけて
Is that so?
そうなの?
Is it my fault?
自分が悪いんちゃう?
This is related,
これ関係あるもん、
So.
それで
What do you think?
どう 思う?
Alcohol.
お酒
That must be Reina's fault too.
それもレイナちゃんが悪いでしょうね
What I did.
自分のしたことや
When?
いつだろう?
Can I give it back?
返せるの?
When?
いつだろう?
It still seems impossible.
まだ無理そうです
Is it still not possible?
まだ無理の?
When?
いつなんじゃ?
Can I do it anytime?
いつでもやっていいの?
this.
これ
I mean, why do you think Reina and that guy are compatriots?
ていうかなんでレイナ奴かんと同胞とかするわけだ
Will it be found out?
バレる?
I'm telling you.
言うてるよ
You don't want to give it back?
返す気ないんちゃうの?
What should I do?
どうすんの?
I'll pay it now.
すぐ払います
I don't have it right now, even if I say so right away.
すぐ言うても今持ってないから
I don't like it.
嫌です
yes.
はい
Take out your stomach.
お腹出しとる
Please stop.
やめてください
Why to him?
彼になんで?
I want to quit.
やめたいです
Want to quit?
やめたい?
I'll stop after paying.
お金払ったらやめよう
That's impossible.
無理や
No, what should I do?
ダメどうしよう
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Please stop.
やめてください
If you're bae, stop.
ベーってしたらやめだろ
Why don't you take it down?
下出してみ?
I don't like it.
嫌です
I want to quit.
やめたいです
It's impossible.
無理です
I don't like it.
嫌です
Well, let me tell you about your mother.
じゃあ お母さんの話させて
Dislike
嫌
is.
です
Shall I call your mother?
お 母さん電話しようか
Give me your phone.
電話を教えて
電話
Lend me your cell phone.
携帯貸してほら
Shall I call you?
電話しようか
I don't like it.
嫌です
Should I use a belt tool?
ベルトツールしようか
Please stop.
やめてください
Please don't quit.
やめないでください
Is that what your mother said?
お 母さんの言うか
I don't like it.
嫌です
Don't send them home if they seem to resist too much.
あんまり抵抗しそうとは、 家の方に送り付けないでください
I don't like it.
嫌です
Are you wondering?
お前不思議?
Because you are strong.
お前は強いもんだから
If I tell you about you,
お前のことを教えたら、
Let's put it in the back.
後 ろに置いてみよう
I don't like it.
嫌です
Why am I lending it to you?
なんでお前に貸してんの?
Do it manually.
手動けよ
Are you still with your boyfriend?
彼氏とまだ続いてるの?
Divided?
分かれた?
Did you finally fall to the ground?
最後に絶地した?
It was quite a while ago.
結構前でした
Quite a while ago.
結構前な
To be honest, when?
ぶっちゃけいつの?
How many days ago?
何日前?
One week is fine.
一週間で結構な
It's accumulated quite a lot.
結構溜まってんじゃん
What if I do it for a week?
一週間やったら?
I don't like it.
嫌です
If you resist, the bottom will break.
抵抗しとったら下が壊れるで
I don't like it.
嫌です
Even though I said I didn't like it, I fell asleep many times.
嫌だって言ってるわりには 何回も寝込んだな
Still not sensitive.
相変わらず敏感さない
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
You're happy.
幸せだね
I didn't give it back on purpose because I didn't want to get hit.
やられたくてわざと返さなかった
Do you like not committing crimes?
犯さないの好きなの?
Do you like it when you don't give it back?
返さないの好きなのか?
Did you return it?
返したのか?
I'll go again.
また行く
go.
行く
Spread it out.
広げてごらん
For this one.
こっち向け
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
It feels really good.
ちゃんと気持ちいいです
I'll go.
行くよ
go.
行く
It's not over yet.
まだ終わりじゃないから
Got it?
分かった?
Let's go back later.
後は戻ってこう
Think about your financial arrangements.
お金の段取りを考えておく